yellowpages.travel 2010-11-01

# Privacy policy - Yellow Pages Travel Directory - YELLOWPAGES.travel

**Copyright**

The content of this site, including but not limited to the text and images herein and their arrangement, are copyright (c) 1996-2002 by YELLOWPAGES.travel. All Rights Reserved.   
YELLOWPAGES.travel hereby authorizes you to copy and display the content herein, but for your personal, non-commercial use only. Any copy you make must include this copyright notice. If attribution to YELLOWPAGES.travel is included, limited quotations from the content are hereby permitted. You may not copy or display for redistribution to third parties for commercial purposes any portion of the content without the prior written permission of YELLOWPAGES.travel. 

**No Implied Licenses**

Nothing contained herein shall be construed as conferring by implication, estoppel, or otherwise any license or right under any patent, trademark, copyright (except as expressly provided above), or proprietary rights of YELLOWPAGES.travel or of any third party. 

**The Content**

YELLOWPAGES.travel makes no representations about the suitability of the content of this site for any purpose. All content is provided "as is" without any warranty of any kind. YELLOWPAGES.travel hereby disclaims all warranties and conditions with regard to the content, including but not limited to all implied warranties and conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, title, and non-infringement. In no event shall YELLOWPAGES.travel be liable for any special, indirect, exemplary, or consequential damages or any damages whatsoever, including but not limited to loss of use, data, or profits, without regard to the form of any action, including but not limited to contract, negligence, or other tortious actions, arising out of or in connection with the use, copying, or display of the content.   
Although YELLOWPAGES.travel believes the content to be accurate, complete, and current, YELLOWPAGES.travel makes no warranty as to the accuracy, completeness or currency of the content. It is your responsibility to verify any information before relying on it. The content of this site may include technical inaccuracies or typographical errors. From time to time changes are made to the content herein. YELLOWPAGES.travel may make changes in the products and/or the services described herein at any time.   
Any opinions expressed herein are solely those of the creators of the material and are not the opinions of YELLOWPAGES.travel, its subsidiaries, or its affiliates, or the management of those entities. 

**Links to Other Sites**

Some of the sites listed as links herein are not under the control of YELLOWPAGES.travel. Accordingly, YELLOWPAGES.travel makes no representations whatsoever concerning the content of those sites. The fact that YELLOWPAGES.travel has provided a link to a site is NOT an endorsement, authorization, sponsorship, or affiliation by YELLOWPAGES.travel with respect to such site, its owners, or its providers. YELLOWPAGES.travel is providing these links only as a convenience to you. YELLOWPAGES.travel has not tested any information, software, or products found on these sites and therefore cannot make any representations whatsoever with respect thereto.   
There are risks in using any information, software, or products found on the Internet; and YELLOWPAGES.travel cautions you to make sure that you completely understand these risks before retrieving, using, relying upon, or purchasing anything via the Internet. 

**Information Provided by You**

Any information provided by you to YELLOWPAGES.travel, including but not limited to feedback, data, questions, comments, suggestions, or the like, shall be deemed to be non-confidential; YELLOWPAGES.travel shall have no obligation of any kind with respect to such information and shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute the information to others without limitation. Additionally, YELLOWPAGES.travel shall be free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques contained in such information for any purpose whatsoever, including but not limited to developing, manufacturing, and marketing products incorporating such information. 

**Trademarks**

YELLOWPAGES.travel and the YELLOWPAGES.travel logo are trademarks of YELLOWPAGES.travel. All other trademarks are either owned by YELLOWPAGES.travel or by other companies. 

**Privacy**

We at YELLOWPAGES.travel are constantly striving to provide excellent service to you, our customers and business partners, while building a long-lasting relationship with you. To achieve these goals, we occasionally need information about you when you visit our site.   
First and foremost, YELLOWPAGES.travel respects your right to privacy. When you visit YELLOWPAGES.travel, you may be providing information to YELLOWPAGES.travel on two different levels about your visit: 

  * Anonymous statistics collected as you browse the site, 

  * And personal information you knowingly give us. 

We want you to be aware of how we handle this information. 

**_Our Commitment to Your Privacy_**  
YELLOWPAGES.travel would like to assure you that we do not: 

  * Collect personal information from you unless you provide it to us. 

  * Provide or sell the names and addresses of our customers [site users] to outside vendors. 

YELLOWPAGES.travel does: 

  * Safeguard customers' information from unauthorized access. 

  * Collect, maintain and use customer information as necessary to provide the most helpful and targeted products and services to meet customers' needs (e.g. customer care or new products or services). 

  * Honor customers' requests to remove their names from our telephone or mail solicitation lists. (Just contact us.). 

  * Maintain confidentiality of customer information when undertaking projects with other companies. 

YELLOWPAGES.travel has always valued your privacy, and we reinforce this belief throughout our organization. Your information will be protected as described unless the specific web page says otherwise. If you have further questions about our privacy policy, please contact us. 

**Information this Site Gathers/Tracks**

**_Statistics about your visit_**  
As you browse the site, YELLOWPAGES.travel's computers collect information about your visit, not about you personally. Via web server logs and browser cookie files, we monitor statistics such as: 

  * How many people visit our site 

  * Which pages people visit on our site 

  * From which domains our visitors come (e.g., "aol.com") 

  * Which browsers people use to visit our site 

While we gather this information, none of it is associated with you as an individual. We use these statistics to improve our web site, to monitor its performance, and to make it easier for you and other visitors to use. 

**_Organizational and personal information you knowingly give us_**  
Within the YELLOWPAGES.travel web site, you may be asked to give us personal or organizational information when you ask a question that requires a response, request rate information online, or order a service online. This information may range from your generic zip code, to your specific phone number, account number, a credit card number, e-mail address, organization URL, business description, business graphics, or mailing address. 

**Use of the Information this Site Gathers/Tracks**

**_Your IP Address and Host Name_**   
YELLOWPAGES.travel's web site logs Host Names and IP addresses (when the Host Name is not available) for systems administration and security purposes. These logs are monitored and analyzed to maintain systems and information security and allow us to constantly improve the value and the availability of the web content. 

**_YELLOWPAGES.travel Registration Forms_**   
We encourage all visitors to register with YELLOWPAGES.travel, although registration is not required, except for access to our premium content areas. The registration forms require users to give us accurate contact information (like name and e-mail address) and preferences that help us better serve you. Your name and e-mail address are used to send you information about our company, product updates, special offers, and newsletters. You may change your preferences at any time, or remove your name entirely from our user registry. 

**_Order Forms and Enrollment Forms_** Our order forms securely collect visitor's contact information and financial information (like your credit card number and other billing information). Contact information on the order form is used for order fulfillment and may be shared with our Partners or Resellers if that is necessary to fulfill your request. The information that we require on our order form is only used to process your order quickly and accurately. Your contact information will only be used to send you the product that you purchase and your billing information will only be used to bill you for that product. During the purchasing process, you may be given the opportunity to sign up for future e-mailings regarding our products, services, and promotions. If you sign up here, YELLOWPAGES.travel will share your contact information with other YELLOWPAGES.travel companies only, not with other companies. 

As YELLOWPAGES.travel's online systems become more sophisticated, you may also be given the option of registering a profile with YELLOWPAGES.travel. This would store your name, purchase history, and billing information to make it easier for you to shop and purchase products/services from us in the future. Once profiling is available, you may opt out of this feature at any time by changing/canceling your profile online. 

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small, encrypted data string our server writes to your hard drive that contains your unique YELLOWPAGES.travel User ID. We use cookies to deliver web content specific to your interests and to control access to YELLOWPAGES.travel premium content. A cookie cannot be used to access or otherwise compromise the data on your hard drive. You can choose to change your browser settings to disable cookies if you do not want us to establish and maintain a unique YELLOWPAGES.travel User ID. Please be aware that cookies may be required to complete certain functions on YELLOWPAGES.travel. 

**Sharing of the Information this Site Gathers/Tracks**

The information you submit on the order form is never shared with any third parties unless it is necessary to complete your request. Also, as required by law, YELLOWPAGES.travel will not share customer proprietary network information with other YELLOWPAGES.travel companies, unless you give YELLOWPAGES.travel permission to do so (either online, or via phone or mail). 

**Information Security**

We have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control. When you place an order, the information you submit is encrypted using the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol. 

**Links to Other Sites**

The YELLOWPAGES.travel web site contains links to other web sites. Please be aware that our privacy policy does not apply to these sites. 

**Opt-out Policy**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our Partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. Visitors who wish to remove their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service can contact us. 

**Privacy Policy**

The Site is a general audience site. We do not currently collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen (13) on the Site. If in the future, we collect personally identifiable information from children, we will do so in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (15 U.S.C. 6501 et seq.). 

**Third-Party Ad Serving & Audience and Traffic Measurement Services**

The Site may use third party network advertisers to serve the advertisements on the Site and may use a traffic measurement service to analyze the traffic on the Site. Network advertisers are third parties that display advertisements based on your visits to this Site and other Web sites you have visited. Third-party ad serving enables us to target advertisements to you for products and services you might be interested in. Although advertisers and other companies do not have access to your cookies as provided by the Site, the Site's third party network advertisers, the advertisers, the sponsors, and/or traffic measurement services may themselves set and access their own cookies on your computer if you choose to have cookies enabled in your browser. These third party cookies are set for purposes including but not limited to targeting advertisements to you that you might be interested in, to prevent you from seeing the same advertisements too many times and to conduct research regarding how useful certain advertisements are to you. Note that any images (or any other parts of a web page) served by third parties in association with third party cookies may serve as web beacons, which enable third parties to carry out the previously described activities. Third party cookies are governed by each third party's specific privacy policy, not this one. Please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp in order to learn more about the information collection practices and "opt-out" procedures of third party ad servers we may use. 

**Web Beacons**

Consistent with standard practice within the web publishing industry, web pages throughout the Site may contain electronic images (generally, single-pixel ".gif" images) called "web beacons." These web beacons allow SITE to access certain cookies that were set in a domain different from that which is displayed in the current web page's address bar. SITE's use of web beacons, includes, without limitation, the following: 

  * SITE may use web beacons within the Site in order to count unique users (actually, unique web browsers), visits and page views. Unique browser recognition is possible through the use of web beacons and associated cookies that may be managed by a third party site analytics partner. 

  * SITE may use web beacons to monitor SITE traffic and conversion patterns through our various product and service offerings. For example, web beacons may be integrated into a merchandise product page as well as the subsequent shopping cart, transaction and verification pages. This allows us to determine the most appropriate methods to serve our transaction-oriented customers. 

  * SITE includes web beacons in HTML-formatted email messages (messages in which we are able to include graphics). These beacons allow us to determine whether or not email messages were opened, links were clicked and notifications/offers were acted upon. 

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. 

**Correcting/Update Policy**

If you would like to correct and/or update your Preferred Listing information, please contact our Customer Service Department.
